It's so strange
Is the spirit of speech true?
The guy who's lying
Fell into the sky
I heard so, but
Seems though he is
loved by everyone
The feelings I want to feel
Therefore, it is free
Turned from a mysterious wizardry
Utopia
You're here.
Today too, with just that
I am reminded of the pain of living
The difference between I love you and I'm sorry
It's like the moon and the sun
It's ok, I'll see you again tomorrow
Even the soul that never learns anything
I think of you again
This life too
Turn the page to the next chapter
A song that you turned into stone
I'll walk while humming
I'll laugh knowing I'm not alone
Thick next book
A song that I got sick
I'll walk while humming
I'll walk my lonesome night
I love you
I'm sorry
See you then
It's like the sun at night
Kusushiki flow of time
A soul that has found something important
I think of you again
Next life too